freebibleimages.org 2019-06-12

# FreeBibleimages :: Privacy policy

## FreeBibleimages Privacy policy

Your privacy and the security of your data is important to us at FreeBibleimages and we comply with the General Data Protection Regulation (GDPR). Cookies are small data files which are placed on your computer or mobile devices as you browse a website and are often essential for the effective operation of that site. FreeBibleimages do not use cookies to collect or store information on your name, address, or other personal details.

### Google Analytics

When someone visits www.freebibleimages.org we use a third-party service, Google Analytics, to collect standard internet log information and details of visitor behaviour patterns. We do this to find out things such as the number of visitors and downloads which are essential in helping us run and develop the service. This information is only processed in a way which does not identify anyone. We do not make, and do not allow Google to make, any attempt to find out the identities of those visiting our website or their IP addresses. We do not share this information with any third parties.

### Mailing Lists

Those subscribing to our online newsletter enter their email address but no other personal details. We will not rent, sell or trade email lists with other organisations and businesses.

We use a third-party provider, MailChimp, to deliver our newsletters. We gather statistics around email opening and clicks using industry standard technologies to help us monitor and improve our e-newsletter. For more information, please see [MailChimp's privacy notice](https://mailchimp.com/legal/privacy/).

You can unsubscribe to general mailings at any time by clicking the unsubscribe link at the bottom of any of our emails or by emailing us at [info@freebibleimages.org](mailto:info@freebibleimages.org).

### Further questions

If you have any questions about your personal data that are not answered here, or if you want to exercise your rights under GDPR regarding your personal data, please contact us at [info@freebibleimages.org](mailto:info@freebibleimages.org).

### Updates

This policy was last updated in August 2018.
